To be continued...
I'm so sorry, Yamada. Come on, Runa, you apologize too. I'm so sorry.
I'll tie my hair up, okay?
Excuse me. I'm heading back home for a bit.
I didn't bring over any of the tools I need, so...
Oh, but...
I'll be right back.
Wait, you don't have to do that. Isn't going back and forth a hassle?
Don't worry. It's not far.
I'll be right back.
Even if they bully me, I can deal with it.
As long as I have you, Akito.
Let's stay together forever, even after we're all grown up.
I can't promise you that.
Hi, welcome.
Would you like a plastic bag for that?
Yes.
This is the one you always buy.
It's really good, isn't it? This brand of tea?
Uh, yes.
It's one of my favorites to drink, too.
Thank you for your patronage.
Excuse me?
Uh, sorry if this is too forward, but would you mind telling me your name?
I've seen you in your uniform. It's Tosei Academies, right?
I graduated from there myself.
To be honest, I've been wanting to talk to you for a while now.
I'm sorry, but I'm kinda in a hurry.
Right, of course you are.
Why is she looking at me like that?
I mean, I am in a hurry.
What would I talk about with a convenience store employee?
Well, this is how you always are, you know?
This isn't my thing. I don't get it.
I'm sure it would be better to stay away.
I'm back.
Is no one here?
They look like they're sleeping so peacefully.
I'll just be quiet while I work.
Close call.
I'll tie my hair up, okay?
Oh, my God.
What?
Mr. Yamada!
Why are you here?
I mean, seriously, how come?
I'm your fan.
He's familiar.
What are you doing here?
Well, it's complicated.
Complicated how?
I'm gonna need you to be a little more specific.
What a drag.
No way.
You're really with Akane?
I'm on a date, and this handsome fella is my boyfriend.
I'm not her boyfriend.
Not likely.
After giving it some more thought, that had to have been a little charade Akane was putting on.
She always wants to look good.
And besides, trust me, I keep up with all your posts on social media every second of the day.
There's no signs of a girlfriend.
It's just business as usual, like always.
I'm definitely not misreading you, so please don't worry.
Oh, yeah.
Almost forgot.
The whole reason I came by today was to return something to her.
I don't see her on campus at all these days, and I don't have a way of contacting her anymore either.
These are the containers for all the lunches she's ever made me.
And her plates, too.
See, I never got around to giving them back, so now I've got a whole pile of them.
Just counting the lunchboxes, I've got around five.
So I figured returning them late would be better than ever.
Isn't that way too many?
Well, I'm pretty sure she doesn't want to look at me anymore.
But when I finally started clearing all this stuff, it got me thinking about her.
I made you lunch!
I didn't know if she'd been doing all right since then, and I started getting worried.
If I saw that she was okay, I thought it would give me peace of mind.
I think she's just fine.
Is that it?
What you came for?
To see her, and get peace of mind?
I think...
I'll leave now.
I'm sorry, this was pretty selfish of me.
Akane doesn't need to know.
I was never here.
You can just tell her that her old lunchboxes appeared out of the blue.
I'm counting on you, sir!
Right.
Good luck in your next tournament!
I'll be rooting for you!
Hey, uh...
How much did she hear?
These lunchboxes...
Showed up out of nowhere.
Is that so?
That's a pretty big stretch, you know.
It's funny hearing you say that all straight-faced.
Thanks for dealing with him, though.
Um, here.
This is yours.
Hmm?
Oh, hey!
It must have fallen out without me noticing!
Yes.
I took it off.
Huh?
I took it off of you, while you were sleeping.
Oh.
Is that so?
You did that, huh?
Yeah.
Sorry.
What?
Why?
Not sure.
For some reason, I wanted to do it.
I wonder why.
Wh-what are you talking about?
It's Eita.
Thanks for getting back to me.
Yes.
Okay, can I tell you which parts I don't have?
Oh, uh, hold up a sec.
I'm gonna write it down.
Hmm, let's see.
Hmm.
What's going on?
Miss Akane Kinoshita, right?
Any shift preferences, or the like?
As long as I don't have class, I can take any shift you need covered.
Yeah?
Well, that is good to know.
Since your school's nearby, the commute will be easy, too, right?
Yes.
Our store tends to get a lot of business throughout the day, so I'd like you to come in as much as possible.
Would that be okay with you?
Yes!
I'll give it my all!
Part-time at a convenience store?
I didn't know you were applying for that.
The job's only short-term.
It's the shop near campus.
You know, the one along the road with the long-haired manager?
Oh, that shop, huh?
Let me know when your ship just set.
I'll come check you out.
Yeah, drop by.
But why the part-time job?
Didn't they fix your broken computer for you?
They did, but Eita, uh, my guildmate, swapped out some parts for free, and I think they'd end up being pretty expensive if I bought them myself.
I just don't feel right about not paying for anything.
So I'm gonna ask about how much it was when I log in later.
You're gonna ask about it in-game, huh?
Uh-huh.
Well, yeah.
I guess they did help you out after all.
You'll have to thank them somehow.
Mama!
Hey, they're calling for me.
I have to get back to this group date right now, but let's chat more later.
Okay.
You've been in the ladies' room too long, Momo.
The guys are waiting for you out there.
Yeah, sorry.
I just got a call from a friend.
A friend?
Akane.
It seems she got a part-time job.
Ah, Miss Kinoshita.
Come to think of it, she never comes to our group dates anymore.
She's been pretty busy with her online games lately, so let's leave her be.
All right!
Today's the day I'm gonna find my prince!
Oh, no.
Momo's ideal man sure is taking his sweet time to appear, isn't he?
You can't give up now.
If you do, it'll be game over.
But still, does finding your ideal man the moment you meet actually happen to people in real life?
Hey!
Rorihime!
Akanechi!
Long time no see!
Hello, hello!
This is Eita, right?
What have you been up to?
Oh, not much.
The submaster and I were having a guild meeting.
Huh?
The submaster?
Where?
Over there, see?
Huh?
Right there!
Oh, so small!
The submaster is super tiny!
He's a member of the micro-nest species.
Out of combat, they're extremely tiny.
Sadly, they're treated as a joke amongst the community, but you can train them to become really strong.
Ain't that right, Mr. Takuzo?
Oh, Akane, dear.
Hello!
Hello, I'm Takuzo Kamata.
My in-game character name is Takuzo as well and is spelled out in English.
Huh?
Mr. Kamata?
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
In here, we call him Mr. Takuzo.
Oh, that's right!
Sorry!
Since Mr. Takuzo usually stays in dungeons out of farming moths, seeing him in the guild room is a rare sight, isn't it?
He's adorable!
But if you zoom out even a little, Mr. Takuzo disappears!
I know, right?
Oh, by the way, real quick, there's something I wanted to ask you about, Rurihime.
Oh, what is it?
About how much were the repair fees for the computer you fixed for me the other day.
Oh, my God!
What?
Uh, but why?
Aw, I can't just let you do it for nothing.
What?
What do you think we should do, Mr. Takuzo?
Well, I can certainly see where both of you are coming from, so that's a hard one.
Instead of monetary compensation, how about we compromise by asking her to take part in that plan we were discussing before she arrived?
Ha-ha! Yes, that sounds good to me!
A plan?
Oh, MT! Here comes the Ominous Senpai!
Huh? No way!
Should we try talking to him?
Huh? And say what?
Um, maybe we could bring up games?
Ah, what was it called again?
F-P...
Oh, someone showed up.
Yo!
Hello.
Trash duty? Sure looks heavy.
As usual, the girls can't take their eyes off you.
If you just enter the pageant instead of turning it down, you'd win big time.
I swear, your good looks are going to waste, man.
But no matter how much you say no, the pageant committee still hasn't given up on you.
They even asked me to talk you into it.
I feel for the girls if you ever started dating.
They might cry a whole river.
There'd be a school-wide riot.
So?
Ha-ha!
Are you free today?
You want a game when we get home?
Yamada!
Huh?
You left your phone in class and it's been ringing non-stop!
Okay, thanks.
Huh?
Seriously, what was that?
Would it kill you to be a little friendlier?
Use some charm!
Thank you, ladies!
Non-stop ringing must mean it's Eita, I guess.
Thank you so very much, my darling kittens!
Or maybe you could say, uh...
The vibration on your desk was making a lot of noise.
Too much.
Hence, the towel.
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
Thank you very much, Tsubaki.
Thank you.
For last night's match, we were playing on an overseas server.
So the lag was crazy...
Don't use lag as an excuse.
Right.
Sponsor?
It's FOSS, right?
That MMO?
Yes.
Is it fun?
Uh-uh.
And it's faster now because aside from the GPU, I also upgraded the previous gen CPU and doubled your RAM.
Oh, and I swapped out your hard drive with an SSD, too.
None of that makes sense to me. But are you saying it's like a totally different machine inside now?
Well, basically.
Thanks again, Yamada. I owe you one.
It's fine.
All righty then. Today we'll be having our Welcome Back Akanechi private event.
And to celebrate the occasion, the three of us will be going on a dungeon raid tour full of daring, too.
Let's go!
Oh, I'm excited to go raiding with you.
Oh, don't you worry, dear. There's no need for you to be nervous.
At your current level, you won't have any trouble clearing today's dungeon, so you're going to be perfectly fine.
And both of us will be right there throwing our full support behind you.
Mr. Kamata, whether it's in-game or real life, you're always so kind.
Not to mention your avatar really suits you for some reason. So cute!
Come on, you two! Are you ready?
It's dungeon time!
Yeah!
All right. I'm going to try my best to be as useful as possible.
– Oh, come on, play it out –
Talk about a huge gap!